<Document>
[color=#ffff00][head=3]Section 1: Out Of Character[/head][/color] 

[color=#a4885c]1.1[/color] Be polite, civil and respectful towards other players and admins. Respect their consent, dignity, boundaries, and roleplay preferences. If somebody ever asks you to stop bothering them LOOC (local-out-of-character), do so. Do always bear in mind, that behind every and each player-controlled entity, there is a real person, each with their own feelings, emotions, preferences, and thoughts, and trying to have fun and relax too. 

[color=#a4885c]1.2[/color] Hate speech is forbidden. This applies to both OOC, but also IC interactions. Usage of terms and behavior out of sheer hate or bigotry, will be punished. Playful consensual banter is permitted. 

[color=#a4885c]1.3[/color] Do not ban evade. 

[color=#a4885c]1.4[/color] Do not disconnect during an AHelp in progress (if connection is lost due to Internet issues, open a ticket on the Discord ASAP). 

[color=#a4885c]1.5[/color] Rule lawyering and rule skirting is not tolerated. Neither is ignorance of our rules. Admins get to decide what is good reason, motive and roleplay and what isn't. Admin discretion is allowed, and what they say, goes. If you disagree, feel free to open a ticket or an appeal so other admins can review the decision of that one admin. Do NOT fight back during the ahelp. That's what the ticket is for.

[color=#a4885c]1.6[/color] Usage of third party cheat software and exploits is forbidden. 

[color=#a4885c]1.7[/color] Doing anything that may damage server integrity knowingly (i.e. causing lag, the server to crash, server-side glitches, etc.) is strictly forbidden. 

[color=#a4885c]1.8[/color] It is forbidden to livestream rounds to others or share recorded gameplay outside of Foxtrot Station without consent of all parties involved, especially for the purposes of ridiculing, bullying and shaming. 

[color=#a4885c]1.9[/color] Ghosting with the sole intent of spying on other people's personal activities (especially ERP) is not permitted. 

[color=#a4885c]1.10[/color] Do not spam or advertise (either other servers, or in general). 

[color=#a4885c]1.11[/color] Foxtrot Station is an HRP enviroment, and as such, standards will be kept according to such. MRP roleplay should be the bare minimum standard accepted here. LRP roleplay will NOT be tolerated. Violation of this rule can lead to warnings and potential game bans. Anything that goes against the spirit of this server and what we are trying to achieve here is prohibited.

  
[color=#ffff00][head=3]Section 2: Consent[/head][/color] 

[color=#a4885c]2.1[/color] Both roleplay and ERP require all players involved to be consenting, either through IC or OOC means. If your OOC consent is not respected, immediately AHelp or open a ticket. 

[color=#a4885c]2.2[/color] Roleplay may occur under implied consent when all players involved engage in roleplay that suggests mutual willingness with no OOC objections raised during or immediately after the interaction. However, if at any point one of the players expresses discomfort or objects OOC, the roleplay must stop immediately. The same applies to ERP as well. 

[color=#a4885c]2.3[/color] Be mindful of the differences between in-character and out-of-character consent. While roleplay without consent of the character is allowed and not necessarily against the rules, OOC consent is always mandatory and must always be established and clearly ascertained. 

[color=#a4885c]2.4[/color] It is your responsibility to keep your consent preferences up to date. This is especially important in the event some relatively common actions, topics or preferences (i.e. physical contact, sex talk, gender preferences, etc.) are not of your liking, in order to prevent both you from being accidentally upset, and others from needing to walk on eggshells. 

[color=#a4885c]2.5[/color] While usage of kinks or sex mechanics for gameplay or non-sexual roleplay purposes is not forbidden per se, you must seek consent from everybody who may end up or ended up involved in that scene before roleplaying it out. This is especially important in the event "extreme" kinks are involved. 

[color=#a4885c]2.6[/color] For any role involving you taking over the body or/and appearances of somebody else's character, OOC consent from the original (the owner of said character) is mandatory if you mean to engage in ERP or other controversial forms of RP with it.

[color=#a4885c]2.7[/color] Most importantly, as stated above, consent MUST be obtained before adult roleplay can occur. It is also understood that IC consequences can occur due to the nature of the roleplay. HOWEVER, if anyone is harassing you due to the kinks you enjoy, please Ahelp it IMMEDIATELY. Just please keep the station elements in mind if you are working a job.


[color=#ffff00][head=3]Section 3: Metagaming[/head][/color] 

[color=#a4885c]3.1[/color] Do not metagame (i.e. using or sharing information that your character has no way of knowing or obtaining, such as knowledge on the exact loadouts of antagonists, or things seen or heard while dead). 

[color=#a4885c]3.2[/color] Do not use nor share in-character information gained by metacommunication. Discussion about current round is allowed on the Foxtrot Station Discord server. Acting on information gained through this method however is strictly forbidden. 

[color=#a4885c]3.3[/color] Do not metagrudge nor metafriend (i.e. treating unfairly a character based on the OOC relationship with the player without valid IC reasons). 

[color=#a4885c]3.4[/color] Players are allowed to retain and share knowledge of past experiences and prior shifts. However, treating unfairly a character solely based on antagonist-related happenings outside of the current round, is forbidden (for example, treating someone with more or less suspicion or trust solely based on their character being often an antagonist or not). 

[color=#a4885c]3.5[/color] Players are allowed to form in-character relationships (friends, foes, or otherwise). However, providing high profile unfair advantages or disadvantages solely based on those IC relationships, is forbidden (for example, ignoring serious crimes, demoting, barring from services, giving out abnormally high access, handing out normally highly restricted items, etc.). If you are unsure or got a particular idea, ask in AHelp for approval. 

[color=#a4885c]3.6[/color] Use the text channels for their intended purpose (you may "subtle LOOC", namely the usage of the subtle command for private LOOC talk, if the command is unavailable).
</Document>
