<Document>
[color=#ffff00][head=3]Section 1: Out Of Character[/head][/color] 

[color=#a4885c]1.1[/color] Be polite, civil and respectful towards other players and admins. Respect their consent, dignity, boundaries, and roleplay preferences. If somebody ever asks you to stop bothering them LOOC (local-out-of-character), do so. Do always bear in mind, that behind every and each player-controlled entity, there is a real person, each with their own feelings, emotions, preferences, and thoughts, and trying to have fun and relax too. 

[color=#a4885c]1.2[/color] Hate speech is forbidden. This applies to both OOC, but also IC interactions. Usage of terms and behavior out of sheer hate or bigotry, will be punished. Playful consensual banter is permitted. 

[color=#a4885c]1.3[/color] Do not ban evade. 

[color=#a4885c]1.4[/color] Do not disconnect during an AHelp in progress (if connection is lost due to Internet issues, open a ticket on the Discord ASAP). 

[color=#a4885c]1.5[/color] Rule lawyering and rule skirting is not tolerated. Neither is ignorance of our rules. Admins get to decide what is good reason, motive and roleplay and what isn't. Admin discretion is allowed, and what they say, goes. If you disagree, feel free to open a ticket or an appeal so other admins can review the decision of that one admin. Do NOT fight back during the ahelp. That's what the ticket is for.

[color=#a4885c]1.6[/color] Usage of third party cheat software and exploits is forbidden. 

[color=#a4885c]1.7[/color] Doing anything that may damage server integrity knowingly (i.e. causing lag, the server to crash, server-side glitches, etc.) is strictly forbidden. 

[color=#a4885c]1.8[/color] It is forbidden to livestream rounds to others or share recorded gameplay outside of Foxtrot Station without consent of all parties involved, especially for the purposes of ridiculing, bullying and shaming. 

[color=#a4885c]1.9[/color] Ghosting with the sole intent of spying on other people's personal activities (especially ERP) is not permitted. 

[color=#a4885c]1.10[/color] Do not spam or advertise (either other servers, or in general). 

[color=#a4885c]1.11[/color] Foxtrot Station is an HRP enviroment, and as such, standards will be kept according to such. MRP roleplay should be the bare minimum standard accepted here. LRP roleplay will NOT be tolerated. Violation of this rule can lead to warnings and potential game bans. Anything that goes against the spirit of this server and what we are trying to achieve here is prohibited.
</Document>
